[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Hello, hello Dad, the Lunar New Year is almost here,
Alo Alo ba ơi ba tế cũng sắp đến rồi cả
our whole family is bustling with excitement. I'm going with Grandma and Grandpa to
nhà ta xôn xao rộn ràng con với ông bà
buy new clothes, Mom is busy preparing the
đi mua áo mới mẹ cù gì con sắm sáng giọt
house, making firecrackers, peach blossoms, flowers, gifts, oranges,
nhà nhào là pháo canh đào nhào là hoa
pomelos, kumquats, and suddenly... Hello,
quà cam quả bưởi cây quất và bỗng bay
hello Dad, have you come home yet? We're all
Alo Alo ba ơi ba ba sắc về chưa cà nh ta
waiting for you to come home for Tet. The village above and
chờ mong ba về tết đế rồi làng trên XM
below are joyful, everyone is dressed up.
dưới vui ci quầ bên người phánh trang
Hello, hello my dear child, this is the Tet gift
Alô alo con yêu của ba đây là quả tết
for Grandma and Grandpa, and this part is for Mom
quả hệ cho ông bà và phần này là của mẹ
and me. Our house is in Kim Ba, a a,
với con qu Nhà mình ở trong kim ba a a
who is coming home? A a, who is coming home? My dear child,
ai qu đ ta về a a ai qu đau ta về cô yêu
when Dad brings... Grandma and Grandpa, the whole
con yêu khi ba bê B Thưa ông bà cùng cả
family is going to Co Phuc Pagoda. Wishing Grandma and
nhà t lên chùa Cổ Phúc Phúc cổ Chúc cho
Grandpa long life and good health. Wishing
ông bà sống lâu tất khỏe nhá cầu chúc
the children to study hard and achieve success.
cho con trẻ Trâm học trăm ngan tha cầu
Wishing
bách ra K phường Tư Như Ý cầu chúc cho
the families of Tu Nhu Y to have peace and prosperity.
muôn nhà Bình A như thươ nhậ ch
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
Hello, hello Dad, the Lunar New Year is almost here, our whole
Alo Alo ba ơi ba tế cũng sắp đến rồi cả
family is bustling with excitement. I'm going with Grandma and Grandpa to
nhà ta xôn xo rộn ràng cò với ông bà đi
buy new clothes, making firecrackers, flowers, gifts, and flowers.
mua ao mớii mê cùc gì cô sắm sáng dọn
Peach blossoms,
nhà nào là pháo kênh đào nhào la hoa qua
oranges, grapefruit, and suddenly flying away. Hello, hello
cam qua bưởi cây cu và bỗng bay Alo Alo
Dad, Dad, Dad, you're almost home for lunch. Everyone is
ba ơi ba ba sắp về trưa cả nhân ta Trừ
hoping you'll come home soon. The village is so
mong ba về kết rê thôi làng trên XM thơi
happy, the clothes are on the table, the cakes are here. Hello, hello. Many gifts
vui ci quầ bên n bánh chơ alo alo C nhiề
from Dad, this is a New Year's gift. This fruit is for Grandma and Grandpa, and
của ba đây là quà tết quả này cho ông bà
this part is for Mom and me.
cò phần này là của mẹ với con qu Nhà
Our home is in Dad's heart, Dad.
mình ở trong tim
Dad, I'm waiting for you to come home, I love you, I love you. When
v Ba ơi con đu ba về con yêu con yêu khi
you come home, I will tell Grandma and Grandpa, and the whole family will go
ba về b sẽ thưa ông bà cùng cả nhà ta
to the temple to pray for blessings. Wishing Grandma and Grandpa
lên cuộc cổ phúc tổ Chúc cho ông bà sống
long life and good health, wishing the children to
lâu số khỏe nh cầu chúc cho con trẻ trăm
study hard and be well-behaved, wishing them to always be like that.
học chăm ngoan thaa cầu bách ra kinh
Wishing all
vường mạn sự luôn như Y cầu chúc cho
families peace and love. LC, that's all.
muôn nhà bình an yêu thương LC chà hết
No matter where Dad is, our home is still like Tet. We need to know that we will go to the temple to pray for blessings, wishing Grandma and Grandpa long life and good health, wishing the children to study hard and be well-behaved, and wishing them to always be like that. Wishing everyone peace and love. LC, that's all. No matter where Dad is, our home is still like Tet. We
rồi Dù Ba ở đâu thì nhà mình vẫn như Tết
need to know that we will go to the temple to pray, wishing
cần biết C và nhà ta lên chùa cầu muố
Grandma and Grandpa long life and good health, wishing the children to
cầu chúc cho ông bà sống lâ số khỏe nh
study hard and be well-behaved, and wishing them always like that.
cầu chúc cho con trê trăm học trăm ngan
[Music]
[âm nhạc]
[Applause] [Music] [
[Vỗ tay]
I
I